[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the female hormone estrogen?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It reduces muscle mass.", "It decreases height growth.", "It speeds up metabolism."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Greshams Law state?", "correct_answer": "Bad money drives good money out of circulation", "incorrect_answers": ["Stock prices lower when unemployment reaches over 6%", "Every 2% increase in supply lowers demand by 1%", "The first hot dog you eat is always better than the second"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How is the body of the jellyfish oxygenated?", "correct_answer": "diffusion", "incorrect_answers": ["osmosis", "active transport", "photosynthesis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Yorkshire Terrier show dogs have a height standard.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is considered to be the father of anthropology?", "correct_answer": "Franz Boas", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis Leakey", "Robert Bloom", "Eugene Dubois"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The city of Stoke-on-Trent, Staffordshire, England is known as the home of what popular craft and hobby?", "correct_answer": "Pottery", "incorrect_answers": ["Stamp collecting", "Hiking", "Kite flying"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first child born in the White House in Washington, D.C.", "correct_answer": "James Madison Randolph", "incorrect_answers": ["James  Franklin Jefferson", "James  Lee Washington", "James Quincy Adams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why are cider apples used for the production of cider instead of dessert apples?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cider apples give the cider a unique flavor.", "Cider apples are sour.", "Dessert apples dont have a strong enough flavor."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the names of the Autobot twins in Transforrmers: Revenge of the Fallen?", "correct_answer": "Mudflap and Skids", "incorrect_answers": ["Arcee and Chromia", "Scrapper and Long Haul", "Sideways and Grindor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The regular consumption of cauliflower is proven to prevent this disease.", "correct_answer": "Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Asthma", "All of these", "Sclerosis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The top price for a ticket to the Super Bowl I in 1967.", "correct_answer": "$12", "incorrect_answers": ["$27", "$55", "$100"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about ants is untrue?", "correct_answer": "Anteaters prefer ants to any other type of food.", "incorrect_answers": ["An ant colony will eat its own larvae if there is no other food around.", "Bullet ants are considered to have the most painful sting.", "Ants are sometimes put into Thai salads."]}]